Margarethe Cammermeyer papers, 1963-2012
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3: Personal Papers., Bulk, 1963-1968.; 1963-2012.
  This series contains personal materials from 1963 through 2012, including correspondence from Cammermeyer to her parents while she was serving in Vietnam; curriculum vitae covering her careers and accomplishments as a nurse, in the military, and as an activist; photographs of her first wedding in 1965; a yearbook from the University of Maryland; a copy of her dissertation from the University of Washington on Cognitive Disability with Obstructive Sleep Apnea; and other materials. It documents Cammermeyer’s 1965 marriage, military service in Vietnam, personal relationships, and professional accomplishments.
  - Yearbook: University of Maryland School of Medicine and School of Nursing., 1963. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Bride's Book - Marriage to Harvey Hawken - Neurmburg, Germany (1 of 2)., 1965 August 14. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Bride's Book - Marriage to Harvey Hawken- Neurmburg, Germany (2 of 2)., 1965 August 14. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: From Cammermeyer to Her Parents from Vietnam., 1967-1968. (Box 63)
  - Dissertation - University of Washington., 1991 May 17. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Photographs for Passport., 1999. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Personal., 2004-2008. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Psychology Paper on Cammermeyer., 2010 October. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Curriculum Vitae., 2012 September. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Wedding Album - Marriage to Harvey Hawken (1 of 3)., 1965 August 14. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Wedding Album - Marriage to Harvey Hawken (2 of 3)., 1965 August 14. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Wedding Album - Marriage to Harvey Hawken (3 of 3)., 1965 August 14. (Box 64, Folder 3)